gamefocus.ca 2015-05-27

# Privacy Policy - GameFocus

### 

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to GameFocus. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that GameFocus collects, and the ways in which GameFocus uses that personal information.

**Credit**

This document was created using a Contractology template available at [http://www.freenetlaw.com.](http://www.freenetlaw.com./)

**Personal information collection**

GameFocus may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including [contest and mailing list]
  * any other information that you send to GameFocus.

**Using personal information**

  * GameFocus may use your personal information to:
  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send you marketing communications.

Where GameFocus discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, GameFocus may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

  * GameFocus will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
  * GameFocus will store all the personal information you provide [on its secure servers].
  * GameFocus will not sell personal data collected.

**Updating this statement**

  * GameFocus may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.
  * You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
  * Other websites
  * This website contains links to other websites.

[ ](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/pass-it-or-play-it-the-unfinished-swan-ps3-ps4-ps-vita-42611.php) Special articles

## [Pass It or Play It? - The Unfinished Swan (PS3, PS4, PS Vita) ](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/pass-it-or-play-it-the-unfinished-swan-ps3-ps4-ps-vita-42611.php)

California-based indie developer Giant Sparrow chose to take a more artistic approach when creating their incredibly ambitious game The Unfinished Swan. When a young boy named Monroe discovers a swan in a painting has gone missing, he adventures in in hopes to uncover the truth behind its disappearance. The Unfinished Swan isn’t about action as much as it is about uncovering the ambiguous world that it takes place in. But is the game itself worth investigating?   

[ ](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/mailbag-what-makes-your-rose-so-unique-42608.php) Special articles

## [Mailbag - What makes your rose so unique](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/mailbag-what-makes-your-rose-so-unique-42608.php)

Dear Jesse, I've never been super comfortable around members of the fairer sex. I've always been more at ease in front of my computer or immersed in a good game. However, I'm starting to feel that if I don't change something, and soon, this could be my life -- rather than just an enjoyable way to pass the time until something better comes along. I started thinking about the quote for The Little Prince, "It is the time you have wasted for your rose that makes your rose so unique." I love gaming but it's kind of a one-way street and all the time I put into it doesn't change what it is.I have a full time job and my own place so I don't exactly fit the stereotype of the unemployed guy living in his parents' basement but that's not really doing anything for me either. I don't know a lot of people and tend to be pretty isolated in my job.Help,Robot Mike [Read more](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/mailbag-what-makes-your-rose-so-unique-42608.php)

[ ](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/mailbag-may-18-bloodstained-vs-bards-tale-42593.php) Special articles

## [Mailbag: May 18 - Bloodstained vs Bard's Tale](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/mailbag-may-18-bloodstained-vs-bards-tale-42593.php)

 You ask - I answer: Dear Jesse,With the recent announcement of Bloodstained on Kickstarter and the upcoming campaign for Bard's Tale 4 I'm at a loss for who (whom?) to fund. Whips or swords? I've wanted to get in on a Kickstarter campaign and I'm pretty excited for both of these games but is it worth it? What if the game doesn't meet its target? Or what if I end up funding something that was lousy and I'm left with egg all over my face? Thx,Don't want to be an egg man [Read more](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/mailbag-may-18-bloodstained-vs-bards-tale-42593.php)

[ ](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/may-10-2015-42573.php) Special articles

## [Mailbag: May 10, 2015](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/may-10-2015-42573.php)

 It's been a while, fellow gamers, and I hope you'll excuse my absence. As I write this most of my belongings are still packed in boxes (except for the PS4 and WiiU) but I am writing this from a new home and so at least one major hurdle has been crossed. In my absence we've had lots of great questions so without adieu let's get to it. Dear Jesse, I'm in my last year at high school. I'm a pretty typical guy -- I ride a horse, cut lawns for extra money, help out people where I can and hang with this girl I like. Life would be pretty ideal if not for one particular teacher -- Mr. G. -- I kind of ruined his life, but I didn't mean to. [Read more](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/may-10-2015-42573.php)

##  [GameFocus High Fives, May 2015 Week 2](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/gamefocus-high-fives/gamefocus-high-fives-may-2015-week-2-42596.php)

 _“Top Five Unexpectedly Great Games”_

 _There is no better feeling as a gamer then when a game exceeds your expectations. Maybe it was a bargain bin purchase at a local retailer, or a title rescued from development hell that was doomed to fail, or even something that just didn’t fit your personal tastes and you took a chance on it. For the month of May, the GameFocus staff reflects on what video games they have played that were unexpectedly great!_

Week 2 - Tyler Hodgkinson - Staff Writer

##  [GameFocus High Fives May 2015 Week 1](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/gamefocus-high-fives/gamefocus-high-fives-may-2015-week-1-42576.php)

  _“Top Five Unexpectedly Great Games”_

_There is no better feeling as a gamer then when a game exceeds your expectations. Maybe it was a bargain bin purchase at a local retailer, or a title rescued from development hell that was doomed to fail, or even something that just didn’t fit your personal tastes and you took a chance on it. For the month of May, the GameFocus staff reflects on what video games they have played that were unexpectedly great!_

_Week 1: D.J. Kinsey - Assistant Editor-in-Chief_

##  [GameFocus High Fives April 2015 Week 4](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/gamefocus-high-fives/gamefocus-high-fives-april-2015-week-4-42544.php)

_“What 5 Games or Game Franchises Should Get the HD Definitive Edition Treatment?”_

With the trend of recent last-gen games being ported to Xbox One and PS4 showing no signs of slowing down some of the GameFocus staff put together individual lists of 5 games or game franchises that need to recived the full HD Definitive Edition treatment. Be it an old classic, or a recent favourite; anything could pop up on one of these lists, so if lists are your thing (of course they are), read on.

##  [DLC Talk: Bioshock: Burial at Sea Ep. 1](http://gamefocus.ca/special-articles/dlc-talk/dlc-talk-bioshock-burial-at-sea-ep-1-41306.php)

Here we are. The next generation of consoles is among us and it is finally time to start thinking about finally unplugging our beloved current-gen systems. Could there be a better swan song for one of these systems than taking a trip back to Rapture?

##  [What's The Big Deal About Mortal Kombat X Anyways?](http://gamefocus.ca/blogs/whats-the-big-deal-about-mortal-kombat-x-anyways-42516.php)

Well everyone, _Mortal Kombat X_ is now available to be purchased (which I’m sure you have done) and if you keep up with video game news (which I’m sure you do), you would know that almost every single day in the lead up to its release, we were hearing about a new trailer, character reveal, or some sort of news regarding the upcoming game. I have to hand it to _Mortal Kombat X_ ’s marketing team, they did their job; it seems like every person on the planet is hyped about this game (which I’m sure you are).

But aside from a good marketing campaign, what’s the big deal about _Mortal Kombat X_ anyways?

##  [Apple's Most Personal Device - This Year](http://gamefocus.ca/blogs/apples-most-personal-device-this-year-42437.php)

  Apple has finally lifted the curtain on the Apple Watch and, unsurprisingly, it looks good.  Maybe you're crunching the numbers to determine if you can afford the $13,000, 38mm [18-carat rose gold case edition](http://store.apple.com/ca/buy-watch/apple-watch-edition) or the [$449.00 sport model](http://store.apple.com/ca/buy-watch/apple-watch-sport).  No matter what you pick you'll need an Apple iPhone 5 or later running the latest version of iOS, so don't forget to figure that into the cost as well.  Before taking out a line of credit to buy the latest and greatest from Apple I'd recommend holding off and avoiding the April 24th release date altogether. 

##  [Why We Need the Worst Game Ever](http://gamefocus.ca/blogs/why-we-need-the-worst-game-ever-42403.php)

Maybe it wouldn't have been as bad if the sales person hadn't said, "this is our most popular seller; I can barely keep it on the shelves."  My mother and I were in the only video game store in the city.  It was in the basement of a professional building and smelled like stale cigarette smoke and BO.  For passing grade five I was rewarded with a video game.  This wasn't a decision to be made lightly; this would be one of the two games I'd get all year.  I can no longer remember the game I originally wanted but I do remember the store didn't have it.  Instead, the sales person was recommending something I'd never heard of, a little game called "Mystery Quest."

##  [GameFocus Podcast: May 2015](http://gamefocus.ca/podcasts/gamefocus-podcast-may-2015-42557.php)

This time the guys weigh in on how much money they would lay down for some bat-DLC.  We keep the superhero theme running with the best games featuring men and women in colourful tights.  Things round out with a list of the games with the greatest endings ever and finally, a look at the Mortal Kombat family tree and the joy of running an island dictatorship. 

##  [GameFocus Podcast: May 2015](http://gamefocus.ca/podcasts/gamefocus-podcast-may-2015-42557.php)

This time the guys weigh in on how much money they would lay down for some bat-DLC.  We keep the superhero theme running with the best games featuring men and women in colourful tights.  Things round out with a list of the games with the greatest endings ever and finally, a look at the Mortal Kombat family tree and the joy of running an island dictatorship.
